Thank you for the opportunity for today's day and time.
I'll have to do those invocation by the past
for the first United Methodist Church.
Thoughtful.
Thought, thanks for being here tonight.
We're pretty together.
Holy God, we give you thanks for this great city,
and community of I am Oklahoma.
We are thankful for our city leaders,
and for the people who work so hard
to make this such a wonderful place to live.
We thank you for our police officers,
our firefighters, our first responders,
and all the other civil servants,
who put their safety and well-being on the line,
in order to protect and serve us all.
We ask that you bless them and their families.
As we gather here tonight for this city council meeting,
we pray that you would be here among us.
We pray that you would give to us your wisdom, guidance and direction,
as we look to the matters that are before us,
and on this agenda, guide our steps and our actions.
Help all of us to live and to act with character and conviction.
Help us to listen to one another,
and search for understanding.
Give all of us a spirit of service and compassion
toward those in our midst.
Help us to act with humility and integrity,
toward the greater good of all of your people.
And when we disagree, help us,
so that we will not become disagreeable.
Instead, help us to treat others,
the way that we ourselves would want to be treated.
Grant us the courage to act justly,
to love mercy,
and to walk humbly with you,
confident in your goodness and love.
It's in your holy name and power we pray at these things.
Amen.
Thank you.
I pledge.
I echo.
Thank you.
To thank.
I pledge.
supported.
Foreigning.
I pledge.
Relo solutions.
Dear Aton's, M Collection.
I pledge.
Thank you.
if there are other questions.
We'll entertain you motion to your pre-
most approved.
Second.
Low call please.
I.
Four.
Okay.
All right.
I.
Any.
Executer reject.
Whole House.
A green and red armist for use of a lot of trash truck.
Total.
And.
High traveled.
You want to.
Well Kevin's getting ready to make the presentation.
I think Vince probably going to want to have a couple of things in this.
I just asked.
I'd like to point out that my wife works for our best friend,
if there's been a corporation.
So I have to refuse myself entirely from the side
of my pet and nothing to deal with on the side.
From an ethical standpoint, I wanted to make that
disclosure.
Bandit, did you have something you need to just add?
Well, it might be best if the timer
or Kevin were to explain the problem.
And then the go from there.
Yeah, that the document you in front of you is what basically
everybody's agreed to is to add a address
that problem that didn't suit your approval.
OK, Kevin, go ahead.
Basically, at PEEPS on Steve Holmes,
you should be snack attack, you should be at your age.
Currently, with the white trucks,
trash trucks that we've reduced it,
we can pull land, turn around, and on their lock,
back after their dumpster.
Their lock was really full, maybe 25% of the time.
We would have to stop on Steve Holmes, back in all of Steve Holmes,
onto snack attacks, property to get their dumpster.
With our new morning struck, there's
an all-uring thrust to turn around on their property.
With it being in front of, we have to pull in, don't hurt trash,
and then back back out on the Steve Holmes.
We think that is an accident where you should have.
So our proposal was, since harvest bank owns the property,
right, less than snack attack, which in this picture,
which is just area, this is snack attacks building.
This is harvest 18 elements on Steve Holmes, the red right here.
This is a route derived that is fuel there.
It used to be the lead.
The agent seemed to get what's in the very house.
It was sitting right here,
sure must have you remember that house.
We have got with harvest, they have agreed to allow solid waste
to drive in on this lock.
That's already rocked.
I mean, we might have to put a little bit of rock,
regular with a red dumpster is, we might have read
so you can see it a little bit.
It will actually tell you to put a little closer to the building there
and we'll be out quite as much on the property.
Argus has agreed to allow us to use the property there.
They just want a whole harmless agreement,
so they're not allowable for anything like it's her.
We get her trucks get to work whatever.
And being in his drew up their agreement,
they agreed to the document that being in drew up.
As of yesterday evening, they noticed by me
that they have one change that they would like made on that document.
So we're going to ask you a little bit.
not to just table this or to not, but we want to go ahead and talk about since it was already on the agenda.
The one thing they want added is if in the future they sell it, I'm not really sure what,
but they wanted to add something in there where they could sell it, and that is the only change they want made,
but we want to make that change.
Their legal is working on that change to be in the document that he is drafted.
So then when you buy a property, if there is an obvious use that's already in existence,
typically you buy the property with that understanding that that condition is in place.
And what they're saying it sounds like they want to make sure that they can sell that property to someone
without us asserting a right to continue to use it for this purpose.
That would be what it sounds like.
I was not aware of that change, but I certainly understand why they would want to do that.
The other thing that I would add is that we also ran this by our insurance company to make sure that they were okay with what we're doing here,
because basically, you know, they're taking on the liability that we are taking on under the whole harmless.
And they submitted some changes which we have incorporated into the document.
And so aside from this new item, everybody seems to be in agreement with it.
So Ben, those changes that you just referred to from our insurance company were incorporated into the version that our best is seen.
So they've already agreed with it.
Our best is already approved it and then we submitted it to the insurance but then apparently our best thought of this other issue with it.
Like I say, it does make sense to me.
Yeah.
Okay.
Kevin, is there any other concerns that you would have?
I mean, obviously it gets sold in the future.
We can't use that as a round of access.
We have to come up with another solution.
Is that where their dumpster currently is?
Yeah.
Their dumpster is currently on this other side of their walk.
Okay.
Over here, you can't sit in the picture, it's right back.
Right here is the top of their, right here is the top of their awning.
You can stay in the top of the awning.
It is on this side of the awning.
The awning where the gasp up is also correct.
It's over in the northeastern corner of their walk.
Just where the dumpster.
And the building running to the right is the hotel.
Yeah.
This is the hotel.
Well, stay blank.
Just down here.
Are you going to be using their drive to the ATM to in and out?
Just a little entrance right here.
There's a circle driver.
I mean, there's, if something in the future comes about with the way of our trucks and then they'll
they're alive and using their drive, how's that going to happen?
I mean, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, this part, I know would be on us because it's what,
where they'll arrive at us using it.
I mean, if it's a straight, where we can kill it's us, I would assume it would be us.
I just want us to be prepared to understand that we're dealing with not car going through an
18, we're dealing with a trash truck, we see what they'll do to our streets so I can only imagine that,
I don't know what that concrete thickness is, they're right.
I don't either.
Is that, is that concrete that, yeah, over or do you shape that everything?
I mean, I don't believe you, so.
I know the portion out here is, there's a curve around here, but the curve is open, so you can drive
it, so there would be an ocean with a curve.
Okay.
Well, I think Brown raised a good point to the extent that if in the future something happens,
whoever's here at the time, hopefully there'll be some doctorate.
Yeah.
The fact that we acknowledge it, we probably have some responsibility there.
So really, no action tonight, making us aware of it and then it may be on the next agenda with the revised document,
and if being assigned off of it, it may be an individual item or maybe a consent agenda item at that point.
Okay.
Any other questions for Kevin?
Thank you.
All right.
Any new business item, all right?
You need trustee community announcements.
I am 11 as adjourned.
Do we have a motion to adjourn the issue, Amy?
Like a motion.
You're in a second?